<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Saheli</string>
    <string name="step_1_save_maximum_four_contact_numbers_of_your_relatives_n_step_2_tap_emergency_button_to_test_the_functionality_of_the_sos_n_nstep_3_the_app_will_send_sms_with_your_live_location_to_all_four_numbers_and_make_phone_call_to_first_number_the_live_location_will_not_be_a_link_instead_it_will_be_longitude_latitude_and_the_exact_place_wherever_you_are_present_so_that_your_relatives_could_take_action_even_if_they_don_t_have_internet_connection_n_nstep_4_now_saheli_is_ready_to_help_you_in_emergency_situations_n_nlet_s_see_how_you_will_use_saheli_in_emergency_n_nstep_1_whenever_you_go_through_any_unsafe_place_just_open_the_app_and_press_back_or_home_button_so_that_the_app_starts_running_in_the_background_n_nstep_2_make_sure_that_app_is_running_in_the_background_that_means_it_is_in_the_system_tray_n_nstep_3_whenever_you_feel_emergency_tapping_power_button_three_times_will_send_emergency_message_and_call_tapping_it_again_three_times_will_start_a_siren_to_deviate_the_culprit_n_nstep_4_make_sure_that_all_these_6_times_tapping_should_be_in_one_minute_otherwise_you_will_have_to_again_start_tapping_count_from_zero_n_nstep_5_tapping_power_button_again_three_times_or_closing_the_app_from_background_will_stop_the_siren_n_nnote_make_sure_that_tapping_power_button_means_screen_goes_off_or_on">Step 1:- Save maximum four contact numbers of your relatives.\nStep 2:- Tap Emergency button to test the functionality of the SOS.\n\nStep 3:- The app will send SMS with your live location to all four numbers and make phone call to first number. The live location will not be a link, instead it will be longitude, latitude and the exact place wherever you are present, so that your relatives could take action even if they don\'t have internet connection.\n\nStep 4:- Now, Saheli is ready to help you in emergency situations.\n\nLet\'s see how you will use Saheli in emergency:-\n\nStep 1:- Whenever you go through any unsafe place, just open the app and press back or home button so that the app starts running in the background.\n\nStep 2:- Make Sure that app is running in the background that means it is in the system tray.\n\nStep 3:- Whenever you feel emergency, tapping power button three times will send Emergency message and call, tapping it again three times will start a siren to deviate the culprit.\n\nStep 4:- Make Sure that all these 6 times tapping should be in one minute otherwise you will have to again start tapping count from zero.\n\nStep 5:- Tapping power button again three times or closing the app from background will stop the siren.\n\nNote:- Make sure that tapping power button means screen goes off or on</string>
    <string name="self_defense_techniques_n_1_be_aware_of_your_surroundings_always_stay_aware_of_your_surroundings_and_pay_attention_to_the_people_around_you_this_can_help_you_avoid_potentially_dangerous_situations_n_2_trust_your_instincts_if_you_feel_uncomfortable_or_unsafe_in_a_situation_trust_your_instincts_and_leave_the_area_it_s_better_to_be_safe_than_sorry_n_3_stay_in_well_lit_areas_when_walking_alone_especially_at_night_stick_to_well_lit_areas_and_avoid_alleys_or_dimly_lit_streets_n_4_carry_a_self_defense_tool_consider_carrying_a_self_defense_tool_such_as_pepper_spray_a_personal_alarm_or_a_tactical_pen_make_sure_you_are_trained_in_how_to_use_it_effectively_n_5_don_t_share_personal_information_with_strangers_avoid_sharing_your_personal_information_with_strangers_especially_if_they_make_you_feel_uncomfortable_li_n_keep_your_phone_charged_always_keep_your_phone_charged_and_easily_accessible_this_can_help_you_call_for_help_in_an_emergency_n_6_avoid_walking_alone_whenever_possible_try_to_walk_with_a_friend_or_in_a_group_this_can_help_deter_potential_attackers_n_7_let_someone_know_your_plans_if_you_re_going_out_alone_let_someone_know_where_you_re_going_and_when_you_plan_to_be_back_n_8_avoid_getting_too_intoxicated_drinking_too_much_can_impair_your_judgment_and_make_you_more_vulnerable_to_dangerous_situations_n_9_learn_self_defense_consider_taking_a_self_defense_class_to_learn_how_to_protect_yourself_in_potentially_dangerous_situations_n_10_share_your_location_share_your_location_with_friends_or_family_members_when_you_re_out_alone_so_they_know_where_you_are_and_can_help_you_in_case_of_an_emergency_when_you_are_riding_alone_in_a_cab_share_your_driver_s_name_and_cab_number_with_your_family_members_and_closed_friends_so_that_in_case_of_emergency_they_can_keep_an_additional_track_n_11_use_transportation_services_consider_using_transportation_services_such_as_taxis_or_ride_sharing_services_instead_of_walking_alone_at_night_n_12_be_cautious_on_social_media_be_cautious_about_the_information_you_share_on_social_media_and_avoid_sharing_personal_information_that_could_make_you_vulnerable_to_attackers_n_13_protection_against_sexual_harassment_the_sexual_harassment_of_women_at_workplace_prevention_prohibition_and_redressal_act_2013_provides_protection_to_women_from_sexual_harassment_at_the_workplace_women_have_the_right_to_file_a_complaint_and_seek_redressal_under_this_law_n_14_rotection_against_domestic_violence_the_protection_of_women_from_domestic_violence_act_2005_provides_legal_protection_to_women_from_domestic_violence_women_have_the_right_to_file_a_complaint_and_seek_redressal_under_this_law_n_15_protection_against_acid_attacks_the_acid_attacks_survivors_compensation_and_rehabilitation_scheme_2016_provides_compensation_and_rehabilitation_to_acid_attack_survivors_women_have_the_right_to_seek_compensation_and_rehabilitation_under_this_scheme_n_android_textcolor"><![CDATA[Self-Defense Techniques\n 1.Be aware of your surroundings: Always stay aware of your surroundings and pay attention to the people around you. This can help you avoid potentially dangerous situations.\n 2.Trust your instincts: If you feel uncomfortable or unsafe in a situation, trust your instincts and leave the area. It\'s better to be safe than sorry.\n 3.Stay in well-lit areas: When walking alone, especially at night, stick to well-lit areas and avoid alleys or dimly lit streets. \n 4. Carry a self-defense tool: Consider carrying a self-defense tool such as pepper spray, a personal alarm, or a tactical pen. Make sure you are trained in how to use it effectively.\n 5.Don\'t share personal information with strangers: Avoid sharing your personal information with strangers, especially if they make you feel uncomfortable.</li>\n Keep your phone charged: Always keep your phone charged and easily accessible. This can help you call for help in an emergency. \n 6.Avoid walking alone: Whenever possible, try to walk with a friend or in a group. This can help deter potential attackers.\n 7.Let someone know your plans: If you\'re going out alone, let someone know where you\'re going and when you plan to be back.\n 8.Avoid getting too intoxicated: Drinking too much can impair your judgment and make you more vulnerable to dangerous situations.\n 9.Learn self-defense: Consider taking a self-defense class to learn how to protect yourself in potentially dangerous situations.\n 10.Share your location: Share your location with friends or family members when you\'re out alone, so they know where you are and can help you in case of an emergency.When you are riding alone in a cab share your driver\'s name and cab number with your family members and closed friends so that in case of emergency they can keep an additional track. \n 11.Use transportation services: Consider using transportation services such as taxis or ride-sharing services instead of walking alone at night.\n 12.Be cautious on social media: Be cautious about the information you share on social media, and avoid sharing personal information that could make you vulnerable to attackers.\n 13.Protection against sexual harassment: The Sexual Harassment of Women at Workplace (Prevention, Prohibition and Redressal) Act, 2013 provides protection to women from sexual harassment at the workplace. Women have the right to file a complaint and seek redressal under this law.\n 14.rotection against domestic violence: The Protection of Women from Domestic Violence Act, 2005 provides legal protection to women from domestic violence. Women have the right to file a complaint and seek redressal under this law.\n 15.Protection against acid attacks: The Acid Attacks Survivors (Compensation and Rehabilitation) Scheme, 2016 provides compensation and rehabilitation to acid attack survivors. Women have the right to seek compensation and rehabilitation under this scheme.\n android:textColor=]]></string>
</resources>